How do you relax after a stressful day in the office?
在办公室度过压力满满的一天后，你会如何放松？
There are many remedies to help you unwind, but the best solution, according to some experts, lies in the great outdoors.
有许多方法可以帮你舒缓身心，但一些专家表示，最佳方案就在户外。
It takes a little effort to get there but the benefits can be a perfect tonic for our stressed out lives.
虽然去户外需要付出些许精力，但它带来的益处，足以成为我们高压生活的一剂完美良方。
I am talking about the activity of forest bathing.
我说的这个活动，就是森林浴。
The Japanese concept of shinrin-yoku – or forest bathing - originates from the 1980s, when it was introduced as a national health programme by the country’s government.
“森林浴”这个日式理念起源于20世纪80年代，当时日本政府将其列为一项国民健康计划。
Stressed Japanese workers are today still relaxing and reconnecting with nature.
如今，承受着压力的日本上班族仍会通过这种方式放松身心，重新亲近自然。
The Forest Therapy Society has certified 62 forest therapy sites in the country and the forest bathing movement is also gathering momentum in other parts of the world.
日本森林疗法协会已经认证了62处森林疗法基地，而森林浴运动也正在世界其他地区逐渐兴起。
It says: "Just as bathing in a hot spring helps to soak your cares away, going for a walk in the woods is said to have a soothing effect."
该协会表示：“就像泡温泉能洗去烦恼一样，在林间漫步据说也能起到舒缓身心的作用。”
If you’re worried that bathing involves stripping off your clothes, don’t be!
如果你担心“浴”意味着要脱掉衣服，那大可不必！
This is about taking time to wander through woodland with no fixed plan or route and just immerse yourself in the forest atmosphere.
森林浴的核心是花时间在林间漫步，不设定固定的计划或路线，只需全身心沉浸在森林的氛围中。
Some health experts have said that having this exposure to nature seems to promote well-being and that’s particularly good for people with mental health issues.
一些健康专家称，这种亲近自然的方式似乎能提升幸福感，尤其对存在心理健康问题的人群有益。
A study conducted in 24 forests across Japan found that walking among trees lowered blood pressure, the pulse rate, and the levels of the hormone cortisol, which is released in response to stress.
一项在日本24片森林中开展的研究发现，在林间行走能降低血压、心率，以及应激激素皮质醇的水平。
It also found phytoncides - chemicals emitted by trees - have an anti-microbial effect on humans, boosting our immune systems.
研究还发现，树木释放的化学物质——植物杀菌素，对人体具有抗菌作用，能增强我们的免疫系统。
Another study carried out a few years ago by Stanford University in the US, found similar benefits.
美国斯坦福大学几年前开展的另一项研究也得出了类似的结论。
Brain scans showed reduced activity in an area of the brain linked to the risk of mental illness in participants who took a 90-minute walk among oaks, birds and squirrels.
脑部扫描结果显示，漫步于阵阵鸟鸣和松鼠穿梭的橡树间90分钟，参与者大脑中与精神疾病风险相关的区域活跃度有所降低。
One of the researchers, Gregory Bratman, told the BBC: "There's an increasing body of evidence showing that natural versus urban areas benefit us at least emotionally with our mood and possibly also our cognitive development too.”
研究人员之一格雷戈里·布拉特曼向英国广播公司表示：“越来越多的证据表明，与城市环境相比，自然环境至少能在情绪层面让我们受益，改善心情，甚至可能对认知发展也有帮助。”
The evidence seems clear that forest bathing is a shot in the arm for stressed out workers, so now is the time to get out and lose yourself in the natural environment – you could even hug a tree as it could be your new best friend!
证据似乎很明确，森林浴对压力缠身的上班族来说是一剂强心针。所以，现在就走出家门，沉浸在自然环境中吧——你甚至可以拥抱一棵树，就像它会成为你最好的新朋友！